hiphoprx.com 2010-12-30

# Hip Hop RX - Privacy Policy | HipHopRX.com - Your Daily Dose of Hip-Hop

**Privacy Policy**  
Thank you for visiting HipHopRX.com site. Your privacy is important to us. HipHopRX.com “Hip Hop RX” takes your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by HipHopRX.com. Accordingly, we operate by the following principles:

 **Publishing On HipHopRX.com**  
All information and submissions to HipHopRX.com will be used to help create the content, services and targeted promotions within our site. By submitting material to HipHopRX.com you grant us the right to use, distribute, and promote your submissions which may include the contact information that you wish to be provided along with your works.

HipHopRX.com may also use the information and content that members provide us to increase market research for HipHopRX.com.

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses HipHopRX.com.

Postings to and communications with HipHopRX.com are not private. You grant HipHopRX.com the unrestricted right to use, reproduce, modify, translate, transmit and distribute any material you supply or communicate to the Service (including your identity and information about you) in any medium (now in existence or hereafter developed) and for any purpose, including commercial uses, and to authorize others to do so.

 **Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as 1-Click purchasing, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of HipHopRX.com’s coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

We explicitly ask when we need information that personally identifies you. For example, if you wish to pay for and receive downloadable products, HipHopRX.com may ask you for your name, address and credit card number which will be transmitted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. If you wish to join premium subscription service, we may ask for your email address so that we can send information to you.

HipHopRX.com may occasionally inform you of new news, music, services, and events. We may select other companies to send you information about their products or services, but we are careful about who we deal with; nevertheless, if you don’t want HipHopRX.com to do this, then you may opt out when you give us your personal information, or you may email info[at]hiphoprx.com to request that you not receive such offers.

If at any time you believe that HipHopRX.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email to info[at]hiphoprx.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

We may link to other sites which may ask you for your personal information to fulfill orders for products; please review the privacy policies of these companies for further information. For more information about protecting your privacy, see the Electronic Privacy Information Center (http://www.epic.org).

 **Third Parties**  
We also use third party advertisements on HipHopRX.com to support our site. Some of these companies (such as Google through Google Adsense Program) may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by [Google](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

 **Passwords**  
Many aspects of HipHopRX.com interactions depend on the reputation and respect that is built up through a history of valued contributions. User passwords are the only guarantee of the integrity of a user’s identity. All users are encouraged to select strong passwords and to never share them. No one shall knowingly expose the password of another user to public release either directly or indirectly.

If you lost your password to at HipHopRX.com, you can [retrieve it here](http://www.hiphoprx.com/wp-login.php?action=lostpassword). You will need to have access to the e-mail account that you registered with.

 **Sharing information with third parties**  
HipHopRX.com will try to provide a site of good quality service for everyone within our database which requires us to ask for certain contact and other information. We will use the information and content to further advance HipHopRX.com.

HipHopRX.com will not sell or share private information, such as email addresses, with third parties, unless you agree to release this information, or it is required by law to release the information.

 **Email Alerts**  
If you subscribe to an email alert, your address will receive emails from that list when ever new news is available. You may opt-out from any email alert at anytime by logging into your account or clicking the unsubscribe link in your email or by contacting HipHopRX.com.

 **Access to Info**  
Access to personal information is strictly controlled and limited to certain individuals within HipHopRX.com. We want to protect the integrity of your personal information that we may have in our database. If your email address changes and you would like to continue receiving any of our mailings, please notify us at info[at]hiphoprx.com so we can update our records accordingly.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the HipHopRX.com online privacy policy for this site or its implementation you may contact using [‘Contact Us’ link](http://www.hiphoprx.com/contact/) or at: info[at]hiphoprx.com.
